[
  {
    "question" : "Who is Technoblade?",
    "answers" :
    [
      "Minecraft Hypixel Admin", "Youtuber"
    ],
    "correctAnswer" : "Youtuber"
  },
  {
    "question" : "Who was Technoblade’s opponent in the Great Potato war saga?",
    "answers" :
    [
      "im_a_squid_kid", "Technostink"
    ],
    "correctAnswer" : "im_a_squid_kid"
  },
  {
    "question" : "True or False: Technoblade once conquered SMP Earth",
    "answers" :
    [
      "True", "False"
    ],
    "correctAnswer" : "True"
  },
  {
    "question" : "Who trapped Technoblade in a water cage prior to the festival in Dream SMP?",
    "answers" :
    [
      "Dream", "Fundy"
    ],
    "correctAnswer" : "Fundy"
  },
  {
  "question" : "Technoblade did what in his one million subscriber special?",
  "answers" :
  [
    "Face Reveal", "Elbow Reveal"
  ],
  "correctAnswer" : "Elbow Reveal"
  },
  {
    "question" : "Name Technoblade’s favorite philosopher.",
    "answers" :
    [
      "Sun Tzu", "Laozi"
    ],
    "correctAnswer" : "Sun Tzu"
  },
  {
    "question" : "True or False: Technoblade won the $100,000 Mr. Beast Duel with Dream",
    "answers" :
    [
      "True", "False"
    ],
    "correctAnswer" : "True"
  },
  {
    "question" : "Name Technoblade’s dog in real life",
    "answers" :
    [
      "Puff", "Floof"
    ],
    "correctAnswer" : "Floof"
  },
  {
    "question" : "Which one of the following is Technoblade’s nickname?",
    "answers" :
    [
      "Technothepig", "Tenochtitlan, Mexico"
    ],
    "correctAnswer" : "Technothepig"
  },
  {
    "question" : "Technoblade used which mathematical theorem in the Dream duel?",
    "answers" :
    [
      "Kepler's 3rd Law", "Pythagorean Theorem"
    ],
    "correctAnswer" : "Pythagorean Theorem"
  },
  {
    "question" : "Technoblade used to play which game before Minecraft?",
    "answers" :
    [
      "Cave Game Beta", "Team Fortress 2"
    ],
    "correctAnswer" : "Team Fortress 2"
  },
  {
    "question" : "Technoblade received which rank on Hypixel after winning the prestigious Minecraft Mondays week one?",
    "answers" :
    [
      "The Pig Rank", "The Blade Rank"
    ],
    "correctAnswer" : "The Pig Rank"
  },
  {
    "question" : "How much did Technoblade single-handedly raise for charity in the Minecraft Ultimate Hunger Games?",
    "answers" :
    [
      "$11,625", "$1,145,294"
    ],
    "correctAnswer" : "$11,625"
  },
  {
    "question" : "What is Technoblade’s signature motto?",
    "answers" :
    [
      "GGWP nerd!", "Technoblade neva dies."
    ],
    "correctAnswer" : "Technoblade neva dies."
  },
  {
    "question" : "What is Technoblade’s Twitter Bio?",
    "answers" :
    [
      "the second worst thing to ever happen to those orphans", "the winner of the $100,000 duel with Dream!"
    ],
    "correctAnswer" : "the second worst thing to ever happen to those orphans"
  }
]